{
    "subject": "resource/Amy_Mastura",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/Malaysia",
    "human_readable": "Amy Mastura was born in Malaysia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.947944700717926,
            "question": "Is Amy Mastura Malaysian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8262225985527039,
            "question": "Where was Amy Mastura born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5481659173965454,
            "question": "What country is associated with Amy Mastura's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3957005441188812,
            "question": "Where might Amy Mastura have grown up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38252460956573486,
            "question": "Does Amy Mastura's birthplace offer any clues about her culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24100680649280548,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Amy Mastura?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19677622616291046,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Malaysia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12756851315498352,
            "question": "What languages are spoken in Malaysia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08617734909057617,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Malaysia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0858793780207634,
            "question": "What are some popular traditions in Malaysia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Amy Mastura was born in Malaysia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2636_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Malaysia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2636_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What languages are spoken in Malaysia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2636_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people from Malaysia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2636_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2636_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2636_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2636_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2636_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2636_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2636_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2636_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2636_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2636_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2636_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the provided context information, specifically from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2636/re-ranker-msmarco/52.txt, Amy Mastura was born in Batu Gajah, Perak, Malaysia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Amy Mastura's birthplace, stating that she was born on May 10, 1971, in Batu Gajah, Perak, Malaysia. This supports the statement that Amy Mastura was born in Malaysia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}